Winner accomplished.
>> Junkyard Love podcast.
5 4 3 2
>> Well, Sigmar, welcome to the Junkyard
Love podcast, man. Thank you one more
time for your time. I appreciate you,
>> Jacob. Thank you for having me.
>> Yeah, I I'm looking forward to it, man.
Uh, like I was just telling you, I've
I've really loved exploring your
journey, exploring what you're all
about. Uh, there's a lot of fascinating
stuff. Anybody listening right off the
bat, look down in the description. All
of his links are there. You can check
out Love Tuner more. But starting us off
here, Sigar, if someone has clicked on
this because it looks kind of curious.
They don't know anything about you,
they've never heard of you, here's the
most impossible question for you. Who
are you and what is it that you do?
>> Uh, so I'm the founder of of Love Tuna.
And Love Tuna is this little device
here. It's a meditation device. So it's
basically a combination of uh sound
healing and breath work. So you take a
conscious breathing break. You arrive in
the here and now and on a spiritual
level you invite the frequency of love
or power of love into your life. So and
why the power of love is because it's
calibrated to 520 Hz. So this is this
little tuner here that vibrates on 520
Hz. what is understood the miracle tone
or the love frequency the DNA repair. So
what you basically do you blow through
this little whistle makes this tone this
frequency connects into your body
physically aligns your water molecules
gives you the feeling of relaxation you
do a profound breathing cycle yeah and
that's already half of of the rant if
you want to call it and then it's also a
shortcut to meditation.
>> Yeah. Oh man there's a lot of exciting
doors to open there. Okay. So, before we
get into more details about the actual
Love Tuner, how did you specifically
stumble upon this? Like, why would this
be an interesting thing for you to
create?
>> Um, I I relocated uh from Europe like a
little bit not 20 years ago to to the
United States. I was in New York before
and 20 years ago I moved to California
and I started right then actually
meditating and it became a important
part of my life. It helped me, you know,
regulate stress and I was always
outdoorsy person, you know, but I was
super busy. I was in fashion, I was in
design and that's my background as an
architect as well. And um and my main
outlet was always nature, you know, like
whatever surfing, running, hiking,
whatever you do. And obviously you
breathe a lot when you swim and and all
those activities. And sometimes this
stuff was not enough anymore. And this
is when you know I started meditating
and it was something that really helped
me that grounded me in the morning. I
did it very richly every morning every
night. And so about a couple of years
into this meditation journey I got
turned on to the frequency of 528 hertz.
And I had no clue like most of your
listeners probably don't know now. I
mean now we're 20 years later so a lot
of people know about it. But uh I had no
clue what the 528 Hz frequency is. We
did a guided uh breast work meditation
and the person brought in speakers and
it was not from YouTube. It was not from
a device. He literally had speakers and
he had the original tone and he guided
us through a meditation that took about
an hour long. He called it the awa
journey and he helped us with breath
work and this sound to go into a
meditative state. And it was in my
experience. It was the most profound
one. It was literally something where I
went like, "Wow, this was the most
profound meditation I ever had. It was
the most profound uh experience I had
and the most connection I ever felt to
my own heart." You like really getting
out of your head into your heart and
have this overall understanding about
what actually the universe is and what
the cosmos is, that everything is one
and one and all. So little did I know
that this becomes my own journey. So um
the person that introduced me to this
breastwork facilitator was an old friend
of mine that was back then already
working on the idea of creating um a
meditation device with now is the love
tuner and and we have been communicating
for a couple of months and at one point
I said to listen come to California
let's sit down let's make this this
product and I was you know I was a
fashion designer I was a uh an architect
so it was easy for me to make a product
and then yeah a couple of months later
we had this product in our hand and we
started this journey and the whole thing
was and this is why we have on all our
devices we have a slogan on this called
one journey because it was literally
it's the one journey that we're all on
and um and love Juno was never I mean
now it's a commercial company you know
it's a e-commerce company and we're
selling in the internet and whatnot uh
but uh it started as a love and peace
mission because we literally
We actually found that this is the most
profound connection to our heart. So
this frequency triggers something in you
that makes you really we talk about
heart coherent. You know when you're in
coherent with your thoughts and with
your heart, but this even takes it to
the next level. It takes it out of your
head into your heart. So you really feel
what where actually our feelings are
coming from or should be coming from.
You know where we actually should live
our life, you know. This is heartbased
and and uh on a on a heart level
humanity is totally connected you know
there's no there's no disconnect you
know so hearts are always curious the
energy of hearts is about 55,000 times
more um uh stronger the magnetic field
than the magnetic field of the brain for
example and still we only you know
believe what the brain just tells us but
if we are hard focused and we live on
this level and what our hearts are doing
is basically they are curious. They want
to connect to another heart energy. And
what literally separates us is our
intellect. So if we would just live on
this hard level, we could be really like
whatever what the hippie movement was,
all love and peace and no more war. But
I'm I mean I'm not a hippie, but I'm a
very big believer in in this concept.
And I think if we would all focus on
this and really go on our heart level
and make heartfelt decisions, I think we
could overcome separation and uh and
unify humanity. So this is how love
junior came. It was a love and peace
mission. It still is a love and peace
mission. It's literally about literally
about unifying hearts.
>> Yeah. Wow. Oh, so incredible. Okay, man.
I was thinking about you were talking
about kind of our our intellect, you
know, sort of versus our heart as if
they're kind of like two different
places for us to to live from or act
from in in in a way. Um, I myself I'm
into meditation and so, you know, these
are not super unusual things for me to
hear. I I can do guided meditations
where I can kind of actively drop into
my heart from my head. You can kind of
notice these very subtle little things.
Um, but I I do think about, you know, me
seven, eight years ago before I really
got into meditation. I'm not sure what I
would be hearing when I'm here in a
conversation like this. So, I wonder
Sigma, I feel like you'd be able to
explain this pretty well. Can you
explain a little bit more about this?
Like, what's the difference between
living in your intellect kind of in your
head versus living in your heart and and
what does that feel like?
Um I mean we we are firing about 75,000
SS a day and if we don't start like
having kind of a s hygiene like a
spiritual hygiene to stop this thought
process even if it's a couple of minutes
when you meditate you know it takes
about 20 minutes a session of meditation
and you will get mainly a couple of
minutes out of it you know where you
really in this process we talk about
mindfulness but basically where you're
mindless you where you're really in your
heart center and this is a reset button.
So this is just basically everybody
understands when you work out and you're
sore you take a massage or whatever you
do uh and this similar is for our brain.
So this is basically the physical aspect
of meditation and then obviously comes
the spiritual aspect and you know the
connection to God or the connection to
the source and u and as you just
explained you have a meditation practice
and for me the love tuner was was so
profound when I experienced this
frequency that I said the concept of
meditation sounds for so many people
like oh my god that sounds cool but I
never have time for it. Um when when we
introduced the love tune we talked about
chakra healing and I said listen if we
call it chakra we lose 99% of people
because yeah everybody understands the
energy field but chakra is something
where everybody goes listen I'm stressed
out you know I have no time for this I
prefer to have a beer you know or a
cocktail whatever that helps me to slow
down to unwind and this is why the love
jun I always call it like it's kind of
cheating because it's it's a shortcut to
meditation and why it is it a shortcut
to meditation and this is why it makes
it simple for people is we all know that
brea that breath can regulate our
nervous system. So, you know, when
you're fired up and you're like
breathing way too fast, you barely get
any any oxygen in your brain, you're a
shallow breather and then you do this
relaxing breath work like inhale,
exhale, inhale, exhale. Similar to
smoking a cigarette or a vape, you know,
this is why it's so relaxing for a lot
of people when they smoke cigarettes.
You know, besides the whatever the the
chemical um bad effects of a cigarette
or a vape, but the actual inhale exhale
is good for us. You know this gives you
the feeling of relaxation. So this is
why the love tuna is basically a
shortcut to meditation. So it it hammers
exactly into where all the doubters are
actually there where they go like man
I'm stressed out. No time for
meditation. What breast work? I have no
time to go to breast work class or all
this stuff. I have no time for yoga or
this is too woo woo for me. Whatever
people say. But this combines one thing.
So it really regulates your nervous
system because everybody can breathe. So
you breathe through this device and then
the frequency vibrates within your body
and also outside of your body. And and
this is what I wanted. I wanted to have
a device for someone that doesn't want
to read five books, that doesn't want to
go to a workshop, but still understands
that maybe the drink at night or the
cigarette in the morning is not the
solution to have a balanced life.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Of course. Yeah. It's it's a
it sounds much more appealing to reach
for the love tuner than reaching for a
cigarette or you know I always I always
thought uh I've never been a cigarette
smoker myself but I always thought man I
wouldn't mind just a couple times a day
having an excuse to go outside and
getting some fresh air with some people
that sounds pretty nice.
>> But uh yeah I mean so when it comes to
when it comes to breath work itself I
mean I I think there's so much
information about breath work online. I
think a ton of people I mean there's so
many people that it has successfully
helped. Um but I kind of want to talk to
the people who have not really do into
breath work a ton like maybe it's not
really in their lexicon maybe they still
have in that category of like spiritual
kind of stranges that they're maybe not
into. Um because to me I see that when
we're blowing into the love tuner uh you
you've heard of a yoga nidra right
non-sleep deep breath.
>> Yeah. To me, I think of and correct me
if I'm if I'm perceiving this
incorrectly, Sigmar, but um when you're
blowing into the love tuner, it's almost
doing that thing in no yoga nidra where
you kind of pretend you're blowing
through a straw like through pursed lips
and it kind of forces you to breathe out
a lot slower than you would have
originally. And for some people, I mean,
it might have been weeks if not months
since they've even breathed out like
that. You know, like the other ways that
we do it is, you know, we grab a beer,
we have a cigarette, we overeat, we um
you know, we're humans. This is how
we've like learned our coping mechanisms
to lower our heart rate and make our
breath uh you know our our rates per
minute slower. Um so can you bridge that
gap a little bit for me I guess? Um I
know I kind of said a lot there but I
was thinking about like non-sleep deep
rest yoga nidra blowing out uh slowly
and kind of like as if it's through a
straw. How how is that sort of thing
helpful? Yeah, I mean every time when
you regulate your exhale, you know, like
breathing through a straw or whatever,
just like uh there's so many breast
work, whatever box breathing, there's
hundred thousands of different
modalities out there, but the most
important thing is to slow down your
exhale. And with the love tuner, what
actually happens is um I I I know that
Zoom might be not picking it up, but
when I inhale, as I exhale through this
tuner, it makes this sound. And by
creating the sound, it gives me a
feedback on my exhale. So when you just
blow through a straw, for example, or
you do regular breast work, you don't
really know how good your breast work
is. This device gives you a feedback. It
goes right away when the tone drops or
changes frequency. Then you know you
need to inhale again, fill up your
lungs, and exhale. So I don't know if it
picks it up, but I'm trying.
I don't know if you could hear it.
Sometimes soon filters it out. So, but
basically it gives you an audible
feedback and that makes it easy because
breast work you you need to learn how to
do correct breast work. So, this is
nothing that you pick up and go like I
watch a YouTube video for two minutes
and now I'm perfect in my breast work or
also when you do the um the yoga
practice. So, you need to learn it. You
need to go somewhere. Um, with the tuna,
it basically does it right that you need
to read the leaflet and and you got it.
You have right away this breath work
exercise that is just to the point and
then you get better and better. Your
exhale extends. You create a a strong
lung volume. You improve your immune
system. But the understanding of breast
work is the most important thing for a
lot of people to even understand why to
slow down the breast. So, as we talked
earlier, people understand when they
whatever have a cigarette and whatnot.
Um, but the deep breaths is like I mean
I had a grandma, she got like nearly 100
years old and the first thing what she
always told me when I was a child and it
was like when I'm excited about
something and you could barely speak
when you're five, six years old, she
always said to me, "Take a breath. Take
a breath." And she insisted on me like
taking two or three breaths. And then
the communication was like you know like
normal you know like the excitement was
gone the negative excitement most of the
time probably but uh and this is what
what people need to understand. So our
nervous system is on alert. So we are
wired still like if we would be living
in the caves you know and the tiger is
outside and we need to run. So we're
consistently in this so-called fight and
flight mode. And this is still our
wiring. This is not, you know, we don't
need this in our society anymore. And
when you do a conscious breathing break,
what actually happens is you get out of
your fight and flight mode. So you the
the parasympotic nervous system, the
sympatic nervous system, this is what
regulates our nervous system. And when
you do a conscious breathing break, you
get out of this pattern. So you escape
this fight and flight mode. And this
calms your nervous system. You make
better decisions. And it also brings you
in the so-called here and now. So this
is where actually meditation or any
thought or any any heartfelt emotion can
even happen is by being in the here now
and the breath is basically your best
friend. You know you come into this
world and the first thing you do is like
you inhale and when you leave you
exhale. So and in between most people
forget that this is our best friend. So
with breathing correctly you can heal a
lot you know not only your your mental
state but you can also like physically
like you know if you breathe correctly
um you have a better immune system you
know you have a lot larger lung volume
and you're just more capable during the
day you know like you your heart is not
as struggling as if if you don't um you
know generate enough oxygen by breathing
correctly. So this is for me the most
important thing that people understand
the power of breath work and then also
the power of their own heart. So this is
like the combination.
>> Yeah. Wonderful. So what is the um
there's a there's a neuroscientist and a
a meditation teacher Sam Harris if if
you ever heard of him. Um I I like that
he he has kind of like a corner of his
speaking where he talks about uh
meditation isn't necessarily like this
break glass in case of e in case of
emergency situation. Like it's not just
oh you're feeling anxious you need to
turn off all the sounds and get in a
quiet room and start meditating so you
can you know just get calm right away.
You know he he kind of explains that
well and um I I wonder where that sits
for you as far as the love tuner goes. I
mean, I'm sure it is pretty helpful if
you are in those moments you're like,
I'm feeling a little stressed. I'm
suddenly noticing maybe I'm breathing
low and slow up in my chest. I can have
the love tuner. It'll help me kind of
relieve these things. But outside of it
being just like a, you know, I'm a
little stressed, let me, you know, take
a hit of my love tuner rather. How does
it help by, you know, tuning in in the
morning when we wake up or or before
bed, those sorts of things? Like what
are the benefits outside of the
emergency use?
>> Yeah. So, I mean, um, you know, we all,
I don't know your generation when you
grew up, but back in the days when I
grew up, we still had like the radio
alarm, you know, like the first the
first song of the day. Even if you liked
it or not, it was in your ear. So, and
this is basically when when you use a
love tuner, you're setting the tone of
the day, you know, you you're exposing
yourself and as with the loft tune, you
become your own instrument. You actually
become uh vibrant. you know, you vibrate
on this frequency. That's the first
thing what I recommend people in the
morning to do. So, it doesn't matter.
You don't even have to really get out of
bed. Just do this one tune or two tunes,
whatever feels okay when you're in this
state of not being really awake. And
this is very powerful because this is
literally setting the tone of the day.
Everything what comes after is then a
certain practice. So I recommend people
after they get out of bed, whatever they
do, if they go on a run or if whatever
their practice is, then take your time
and do a conscious tuning cycle. So we
recommend like six cycles depending on
the exhale. This can take up to like
whatever four or five minutes. And you
inhale, you exhale. And after this six
cycles of breathing and tuning through
the love tuna, you sit in silence for 30
seconds. And this gives you the real
reset. This is basically your morning
routine if you want to call it like you
know your morning spiritual hygiene your
shortcut to meditation and um and then
when you go during the day this is comes
more to this you know what we talked
earlier when it's an emergency and you
go like hey listen I'm sitting in
traffic and and I'm late or whatever I'm
in front of him before a meeting I'm
stressed out I step outside at tune real
quick so this is this is like let's call
it the emergency tuning and then I
really highly recommen recommend people
before they go to bed because the the
528 Hz calms your entire system and it
prepares you. So when you at the end of
the day take again again again I mean I
always recommend six cycles or more. I
should not do less if you really do a
tuning a tuning session. So you should
do your six cycles or whatever feels
good for you and then really tune the
day out you know also like have
gratitude you know for the day and
prepare for the night because we all go
in this state where we sleep and this is
like I mean we all know what's going on
while we sleep and and you can really
tune yourself into it and a lot of
people are suffering from um you know
like yeah from not getting enough sleep
and and especially our society is so
driven to this eight hours, you know, I
need my eight hours of sleep and I don't
say that this is not correct, but it
also helps you to relax and don't panic
if you wake up at night. You know, it's
like it's something because it's it's I
heard sometime that the eight hours came
up from a mattress producer and this is
why they tell us, you know, to sleep
eight hours. I don't know if this is
true. I mean I obviously try to get
enough sleep or enough sleep for me that
is healthy but I also don't panic when I
wake up in the night because uh I mean
the most powerful poems most powerful
music was written in the night hour so
there there's some magic in the night
too and and if you get this magic uh you
can prepare yourself with the love so
you most of the time I tell people hey
listen it gives you a better sleep you
can sleep through it because your
cortisol level drops because of the 520
Hz frequency. So this is I mean you know
it for sure but this is exactly uh the
chemical that gets produced when you're
stressed out. So you're super tired you
fall asleep you sleep for two three
hours you wake up boom cortisol level is
too high. So the 528 hertz helps you to
regulate this. But I even tell people
even if you wake up and we all know this
like 4:00 in the morning 2:00 in the
morning where we saw this is the
spiritual window. I said if somebody
wakes up, I always tell people use the
tune and just, you know, like lay there
and just like really let the magic of
the night happen, you know, and if if
you feel motivated and you're creative,
get up, write something. Uh if you have
a great business idea, make some notes,
you know, if you have your loved one
next to you, tell what is on your heart,
you know. So, so don't be so anxious
about oh my god, you know, I need to get
up in 4 hours and I'm losing my sleep
because you know we we can regulate
ourselves you know and it's more about
to get rid of this fear of this panic of
like I need to sleep you know it's like
I get it if you don't have enough
sufficient sleep and you have a
unhealthy lifestyle that's always bad
but um with with the tuna I always tell
people tune in to sleep drive down your
cortisol
But if you have this magic at night, you
know, tune a couple of times, you know,
and really enjoy it.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Man, that sounds a lot
better than tuning into, you know,
whatever Tik Tok or Instagram reels is
feeding you at the moment, [laughter]
you know. Uh yeah, you know, I I'm very
human, too. I I struggle with uh from
time to time waking up and the first
thing I do is go to my phone, you know,
and so I'm I'm tuning into the frequency
of whatever the algorithm is wanting me
to care about that day, you know. And I
think we can all notice the difference
when we do that versus we wake up and we
consciously choose what we're going to
consume. We start off on a good beat. So
yeah, love tuner in the morning and the
middle of the night. That sounds like a
perfect tool, man.
>> Yeah, it's I mean, listen, I have it
here too. Makes our life easy. We all
love it. We all are depending to it.
Yeah. But it it it takes a lot of
discipline not to because I'm running a
company. So, you know, like I always
want to be on top of we work a lot with
Europe. So, it's my time zone. Early
morning, I check my phone. I have to
check my phone. But I really try that at
least the first half an hour to an hour.
There's nothing else besides, you know,
my own frequency and whatever rock
somebody's boat, you know, to go
outside, take a deep breath, or use the
option, but don't get interfered, you
know, by by cell phones, computers, etc.
>> Yeah. Yeah. I have a my friend Spencer
who's been on this podcast years ago. uh
he told me this thing that stuck with me
and it's really helpful. uh you know
like a lot of apps when you go to set
your alarm for the morning it'll
sometimes tell you how many hours you're
about to get if you wake up at a certain
time which is like useful and not useful
but um regardless of what it says I
noticed that for a while I was like
getting four hours it's going to be
going to be a rough day whatever and you
know start telling yourself those
stories but what he says he says regard
even if it's 30 minutes of sleep he's
about to get whatever that number is he
tells himself he says that's the exact
amount that I need for tomorrow I'm
going to be just fine time and I started
kind of tricking myself with that too
and it's it's pretty useful. So, anybody
listening who has that uh struggle of
not getting their eight hours and they
make themselves stressed out, you know,
use a love tuner for sure, but also tell
yourself whatever you get, you're going
to be all right.
>> Exactly. Yeah, that's very important.
Yeah.
>> Yeah. Um, man, I wanted to uh I heard
you say a couple like just really cool
facts about uh 528. So, I want to
explore a little more on the 528 uh
frequency just itself. Um,
I I I feel like nowadays, even if people
aren't super into spirituality, even if
they're maybe not musicians, they
probably have heard the 528 hertz thing.
They probably like,
>> you know, on YouTube, you can go, you
know, 528 calm morning mood or whatever
it is. Um, what is so, not only what is
so fascinating and special about 528,
but can you also kind of demystify it a
little bit? So for people who like I
said maybe this not normally their
lexicon of communication, they don't
really use these frequency words very
much. How can we explain it to them in a
way that kind of makes some sense? Um I
mean first of all the 528 hertz is not a
man-made frequency. So it's a frequency
um so first of all it belongs to the
sulfatio tones and the most powerful one
is the 528 hertz and um it occurs in
every living matter the humming of the
bees uh in the chlorophyll of the leaves
this is for example you know every every
frequency has a color on the light
spectrum 528 hertz is green is also why
it's it's the center the solar black is
heart center of our body but in in the
leaves. When you measure a leaf, it
vibrates exactly on 528 Hz and it's
green because of the light spectrum
color green from 520 Hz. So this is just
like a little bit of a background where
it's coming from. So it's a cosmic
divine frequency. It was never man-made.
Uh the second thing is it was never
mystified. It was actually occuring in
our musical scale. So the original
musical scale the regular C note was 520
Hz and the Gregorian choir for example
600 after Christ have been chanting on
this frequency and have been healing
entire communities in in the churches
back then in Europe. The same thing was
the organ itself in the church was
calibrated correctly. So when they hit
the C note it it actually produced 528
hertz. So it connected communities and
um and yeah through history it got
interfered with this frequency and at
one point we ended up with a new musical
frequenc and not frequency but a new
musical scale where the atone got
manipulated and went from 444 hertz to
A440. And what it did is it made the C
note disappear because everything is
regulated out of the A tone. And so 528
Hz disappeared in our musical scale. And
this is like when now people talk about
528, they go, "Oh, it's there's such a
mystic about it." You know, there's what
is this? What is the miracle tone? And
blah blah blah. And then you you listen
to Professor Horowitz and all his stuff.
And I mean, he's great. He brought the
528 uh movement back in the 80s and I
really recommend everyone that is
listening check him out. He tells very
profound stuff. Um a lot of stuff might
sound conspiracy but it's not. It's
literally what happened and there's a
reason why we are not in harmony and why
we in dissonance even with the music
that we are listening to. And super
interesting, John Lennon composed
Imagine. That is the most known love and
peace song since over 50 years in 528
hertz. So he knew about it. And this is
why when people talk, what is it? Is
this woo woo? Is this kind of weird?
This is kind of new age. No, it's super
old. It was always around and this is
how it actually should be. So we are
just bringing back a forgotten tone.
>> Yeah, man. Well, so well said. I love
that. I feel like you you broke that
down so well, man. Uh yeah. Um okay, so
maybe we we'll dip our toes in the
conspiracy side of things for just a few
minutes at least. Why would we I feel
like I've read some things online. Why
would we go away from from 528? Like
what what are kind of the conspiracies
there or what are the um you know
assessments in in the zeitgeist rather?
Like what what do people say?
I mean uh if if you look at how divided
humanity is right now. I mean we go back
in history and we don't know everything
about history if it's true or not but
all cultures have been healing with
sound you know uh all the way to
Nicholas Tesla. He built a frequency
healing machine over 100 years ago. Um
yeah you find on and off somewhere a
doctor or a health practitioner that
that uses frequency healing machines.
They're all out there. But the
mainstream is not frequency. The
mainstream is pills and and whatnot. You
know, all this stuff has frequencies,
but they're not beneficial frequencies.
So, when we talk about about conspiracy,
it's like um if you have people in
harmony, why would they start a war? You
know, why why would they care? You know
what I mean? If you're in harmony and
and and you're happy with your family
and you know there's abundance of of
money there you know we all are healthy
we we never had so much wealth around
the world that we have right now you
know we are so well taken care of and
but we are so divided you know and and
this answers I think this answers the
question of that we are not unified and
you can only separate people by
manipulating whatever they're exposed to
and Everything has a frequency. And for
me, when when I started digging into
this, I said like, "Wow, what people
that are powerful put so much effort
into interfering with a frequency, so
there must be something, you know." And
then on the other hand, we have so many
frequencies out there that we are
knowingly are not good for us. You know,
they're influencing us. So, we exposing
ourselves all day long to negative
frequencies and we are just like in this
imbalanced state. You know, like when
you play a guitar, when you play a
piano, as soon as you hear that the tone
is off, you retune it. We as a human, we
run around like crazy. You know, we're
totally out of tune and we take no time
to retune. And yeah, the 528 hertz, we
align with this frequency. It's it's a
great human retune. You know, you can
retune. You can back you get back into
balance. And in this state of mind, you
know, you just make better decision and
you can access your heart. And this is
what I think uh talking about
conspiracy. I mean, we can go into name
like 10,000 um you know, accidents or
incidents in history where somebody
interfered with something, but the
overall understanding is it's the
separation of humanity and and um and
this is not my take on on on conspiracy.
This is what you see daily, you know,
like I mean we turn on the TV and you go
like whoa, you know, like by the way
talking bad bad frequency if if you
expose you yourself to this kind of
news, it's not healthy either, you know,
and and this is like it's it's it's a
manipulation like some people call it
the matrix. But uh humanity can only
escape out of this conspiracy or
whatever you want to call it by
literally tuning into what is human. You
know what is human and the biggest power
we have is is the connection to the
divine and the connection to our heart.
So this is literally the cycle. And I
think if if if you for yourself
understand how to access this, you just
have a better life quality. And I mean I
always refer to KL Jung. He said, "If
you look on the outside, you become a
dreamer. If you go inside, you awaken."
And that's basically what it is. So, if
you're in harmony, you awaken. If you're
[clears throat] in dissonance, yeah,
that takes a little longer and uh you
need to work very hard on it. And so, I
think it's all about unifying humanity.
>> Yeah. Absolutely. I mean, I, you know,
my background for many years, I have
like 14, 15 years as a DJ and, uh, I've
definitely, you know, so if I'm going
through my playlist of my my list of
songs, one of the, uh, columns is the
key in the keys in my program, um, in
the DJ program, they're actually
colored. And so, you know, like you're
>> you you can kind of relate them if
you're looking at the chakra system, you
know, say break it down to seven simple
colors. you can kind of equate like your
red ones are going to go to your root
chakra, your orange ones next, you know,
like the these different songs, they
have kind of a different feeling to them
when you play them, you know? And so I
can as a DJ I can build kind of a
journey up to where you know if I
started with a heart center song it
might not really resonate but if I build
up from the bottom or even build up
build down um by the time I play you
know 30 40 minutes in by the time I play
that heart center song it's a whole
different experience in in the room or
in the um event that I'm playing. So um
I I've seen it I've seen it firsthand
you know as I get a little bit better at
mixing and key and like trying to see
what happens really in front of me. You
know, I've had some pretty profound
experiences by intentionally like using
my colors, seeing where we're at with
our chakras, kind of tuning into what
I'm feeling from the the crowd and the
audience in that moment. And, you know,
in some ways they kind of select the
songs in a weird way. It's it's it's a
cool thing. But, um, yeah, I mean, I
imagine the same thing can be said
about, you know, churches or um, Kon or
any sort of group coherence experience.
Um, I mean, you mentioned Carl Young. He
he he studies the collective unconscious
a lot. Um do you think that
by you tuning in to 528 in the morning,
do you think that has a positive effect
as you go about the world? Like as you
interact with people, your energy being
centered, does that have like a ripple
effect with the people that you interact
with? Would you say?
>> I I think so. I think so. Like I mean
it's like but it's the same thing like I
want one want to call the the love tuner
like the peacemaker and you walk around
in the tune everybody smiles and you but
just walks through a street and smile at
someone you know.
>> So if your vibration is up people will
react to it for sure. You always have
people that are just so closed down but
in general you know like when you see a
friendly face on the street you know
it's it's kind of like you know you you
react to it in a positive way. And the
same thing as when you, you know, like
raise your frequency or tune your
frequency in the morning, it's for sure
recognizable by people. And even if they
don't get it consciously, but they for
sure get it subconsciously. So you're
just in a better tuned state of mind.
And we all know when we go into a room
and sometimes we have this feeling is it
this kind of off you know this kind of
weird wipe or you have whatever you meet
random people and you have a
conversation and you walk away from it
and you go like wow you know this this
was very uplifting so that's all
frequency so we all vibrate and I think
um the most important thing is like as
we are so run by our brains is that we
have also this kind of thought hygiene
you know like no negative talk you know
no self-criticism, you know, like you
can be you can be whatever try to
improve yourself, but you need to be
really careful how you do it, you know,
and then also always being grateful for
stuff. I mean, gratitude is is a big
one. And when it comes to tuning, like
if you tune in the morning, yes, it
helps, but you need to be also really
aware of, you know, it's not like, oh, I
tune then everything is okay. It it
takes way more, you know, first of all,
you need to be your authentic true self.
So this is where everything starts
because we always talk about love can
heal the world and love is the most
powerful frequency in the universe but
authenticity you know lays the ground
you know authenticity is actually the
key to wholeness. So because if you're
not authentic you know you you can tune
whatever you want to tune you know
because the frequency is just not in
resonance. So it's very important to
scrape away all the stuff and everybody
has it and everybody has to do their
work and then you can start building up
similar what you just explained as a DJ
and I really appreciate this a lot
because I I was very into electronic
music I still am and I I saw the whole
movement to the 90s and uh Ebisa and
whatnot and I have seen this tribal
effects what music can happen and when a
teacher knows how to build it up and
this is why dancing is so important
because it goes to your entire chakra
system. And this is why I always tell
people listen just dance, you know, just
have your chakras flow, have your
energies flow and and open up to the to
the song, you know, like literally and
there's so much what the teaches can do,
you know, like literally starting as you
said with the root chakra all the way up
that you feel like kind of, you know,
like lightminded or enlightened,
whatever you want to call it, you know,
because it touches your heart and then
it opens up to the divine. And if this
is done correctly, this is why I'm
promoting with so many DJs around the
world. I'm targeting them as a listen
guys. I understand it's a big it's a big
money maker. It's it's a big
entertainment thing, but we humans we
always danced together. you know,
dancing unites, you know, it's it's such
a cool thing to do and and it doesn't
matter, you know, like yes, drugs play
an effect in this whole night night
life, but that's totally fine, you know,
like this was always done in in in no
way or another, but the most important
thing is if those people would play the
real harmonic music, you know, where the
key where the C really hits the heart,
you know, that would be like so
uplifting and there's you barely hear a
difference, you know, But it's cool and
I see it now with more and more DJs are
doing it and I know there's big labels
behind it. There's big companies behind
it that are not in favor of this. But uh
I mean as you said you know like you can
really guide and then at one point the
DJ actually follows the tribe if you
want to call it you know and this is
this unifying moment and I think people
that dance together you know it's like
it's it's the most profound thing you
can do. It's it's beautiful. like going
to a church and just uh you connect
directly to the source.
>> Mhm.
>> Yeah. I mean I think of the you know how
many years of human experience were we
just you know we didn't have electricity
for example and so night comes around we
have the fire and let's start playing
some drums and and dancing around like
you know the the amount of culture that
was probably you know
almost invented during dancing
ceremonies. I mean, I I just feel like
it's such a part of who we are. I mean,
especially when we do, you know, we now
have all this important research and we
have science and we could start to like
connect a lot of these dots that um, you
know, we could kind of prove, hey, this
is like you mentioned, for example,
bees. You mentioned that bees, uh, their
buzzing is is 528 hertz. Um, I mean,
that's something that until we had the
the the proper tools to measure that, we
wouldn't know that sort of thing. Um,
and yeah, so it just makes sense that
it's it brings us back to our center,
brings us back to to our um, you know,
our fullness, our our most authentic
self, as you said. It makes total sense.
Um, one one question I did want to ask
for you. If someone's listening right
now and they've never heard of the human
resonance, the human frequency, how
would you describe that to them?
>> I mean, we we talk about, you know, the
frequency of mother earth, of our
planet. And uh and um it's very
interesting because it was pretty steady
for a long long time and in the last 15
years I don't know if you have seen his
researches the planet actually is
raising its own frequency
and uh you need to dig pretty deep to to
find all this information but um the
human resonance is so important for us
to understand that our own planet has a
frequency. So we have a frequency and
this this understanding of of energy of
everything is basically you know
vibration it's it's and frequency this
is the most important thing and with the
shoe frequency it's it's funny that you
mention it because it's raising its own
frequency right now and this in the last
15 years tremendously so what does this
mean our own planet is telling us
basically guys get up and raise your
frequency then this is also Why we see
so much craziness in the world right
now? Because the way
our society is built is not high
vibrational. We are very low
vibrational. You know, we we lost
connection to to nature. We we are
destroying our own planet. And I mean
and uh I don't want to sound too
hippie-esque here but if you cannot
embrace nature I mean this is God's
temple you know like and and there's not
one being in this world destroys it's
its own you know um planet you know like
I mean we are doing it and that's the
craziness. So with the Schuman frequency
it is so interesting because it's
raising the frequency right now and we
we are not doing it. So, and this is why
it's harder on us, you know. This is why
so many people are like literally um
disconnected, but not disconnected from
each other, but literally disconnected
from the universe, you know, where they
where they don't feel they don't feel to
belong anymore. Like they doubt
everything, you know, they're doubting
the divine. They're doubting, you know,
the the cycle of life. They're doubting
nature because it it's really stressful
on them because the planet is basically
telling us raise your frequency. planet,
mother earth is doing it and we need to
really follow and I mean this is the
best sign um in the universe right now
that it's time for humanity to raise
frequency and not doing the opposite to
lower our frequency.
>> Yeah. Yeah. You know, it's very
interesting that our you would think our
species would have some sort of
important part of our culture that
everyone just agrees upon like hey, you
know, all eight plus billion of us make
sure that this is important. We all
focus on like what is humanity and what
are we doing and like what are we going
towards and what's the point of all this
and that sort of thing. I know it gets
lost in in religions and those arguments
start happening. But I think even before
you get to religions, even before you
get to any of like the exact
terminology, it's pretty obvious like
what we're trying to do. Like if we look
at
>> I I always like the example of like say
you were an alien and you're looking
down at the earth and you're like what
are those crazy apes doing? You know,
like what are they doing down there?
like we could probably have a pretty
short conversation and we could all
agree upon, yeah, we're kind of just
doing this, you know, we're inventing
these things and we're we're developing
families and we're loving each other and
we're growing and we're, you know,
growing towards some direction. And I I
don't know. I just think it seems pretty
obvious when we're, you know, growing
away from that or, you know, going the
wrong way or, you know, uh, going
against the frequency of what we should
be of the direction we we should be
going in, you know. So, um, yeah, it
it's just very cool that more and more
people, um, you know, are are waking up.
You know, that's such a a broad term in
so many ways, but I mean, you said, was
it the last 15 years or so, this human
frequency was
>> Yeah.
>> Yeah. I mean, I think in the last 15
years, there's been a lot of people have
had some form of spiritual awakening.
That's for sure.
>> Absolutely. I mean, you know, this is
when way we all talk about, you know,
2020 and the pandemic and whatnot, but I
think it's a good side effect. You know,
a lot of people woke up. I mean, a lot
of people are like in in a deep state
>> to sleep right now and and totally
disconnected, but there there came so
many people out and go like, listen,
that that cannot be. And I think it's
it's beautiful to see this, you know,
because in 2019 we have been doing a
bunch of seminars in in Europe with love
tuna and everybody was like, hey, this
is where we're going to and then boom
comes this this one year and and uh and
it brought a lot of people back to like
giving up completely. So then they never
ever went back to a spiritual path and
and said like okay anyway everything is
is BS and uh but another people they
really awaken you know and the thing is
I I don't believe that the collective
awakens you know what I mean I believe
it takes the individual and it takes one
individual you know to uplift others so
and that's what it is and then it comes
to you know what you decide on what I
said earlier you know if you go inward
you awaken or you look on the outside,
you become a dreamer. So I think it
becomes down to to the individual and
obviously then it will impact the
collective and and I I think it's it's a
very very exciting times that we're
living in, you know, and and everything
is possible right now.
>> Yeah. Amen to that, man. I I totally
agree. Uh man, okay, we're getting up
here in time. Um, I I kind of want to
end this with um I I think what you've
said so far about I really like what you
said about authenticity. Um, c can I ask
you and you know there's of course no
wrong answer to this. Can I ask you say
someone's listening to this right now
and they're on some sort of awakening
journey. They're on some sort of maybe
they're just beginning, maybe they've
been doing it for 10 years and they just
like this kind of stuff, whatever.
They're in some sort of awakening
experience.
>> What message could you give them or um
something to be to carry with them? uh
how do they remain authentic and listen
to their intuition?
I think it's um you know when a lot of
people talk about the channeling you
know so people have channels but at the
end of the day everybody's a channel so
channeling is the highest form of
intuition and if you don't have the
right feeling about something then
that's the answer you know I mean this
is literally like really trusting in
yourself and it's all about
self-empowerment and this is what what
I'm writing in my book about it What I
tell people how to use the love tune,
how to practice it, it's basically like
really trusting yourself because it's
about your intuition and nobody can take
this away from you. This is your channel
to the divine and it's your intuition.
If something doesn't feel right, then
there's something, you know, and you
don't have to find an explanation and
go, "Yeah, maybe the guy had a bad day
or whatever my job doesn't mean this or
this." So no no you have this intuition
and you by yourself you need to be as
self-empowered to really trust yourself
to trust your intuition. So, and I know
especially when you go on this on this
path and it's like sometimes it's it's a
little bit unfair because the people
that awaken they all go at one time they
get lonely at first they get super happy
then they get lonely so they went
through all these phases but at the end
of the day it's literally like tuning
into your own intuition like becoming
this channel you know because you are
living your life nobody else is living
your life you make your decision and
they should be based on your intuition
Wow. Powerfully said. I really love
that. I mean, and it to me, I'm just
thinking it's not an arrival either.
It's like a constant we got to have our
daily habits almost. You know, things
like the love tuner, things like
meditation, things like breath work, you
know, having a a a habitual day that,
you know, equates to you being able to
tune into your intuition, you know.
>> Yeah. So
>> and and I mean you know and tuning into
into your intuition is like you know
spirituality sometimes sounds so serious
but I always tell people just keep it
light you know like really you know stay
the fool stay stay funny stay stay stay
stay stay stay stay stay stay stay stay
stay stay happy happy you know don't
take it too serious for this we have
religion
>> yeah amen amen yeah oh man keeping it
light all right well oh Sigmar thank you
so much for this man I feel like you're
such a wealth of information I really
enjoyed getting to not only learn about
you know your products and your journey
but getting to talk you in in and being
able to ask you all these questions to
your face is is truly a gift. So, uh,
one more time, man. Thank you so much
for for spending this time with me,
buddy.
>> Awesome. Thank you so much, Jacob, for
having me.
>> Yeah. Yeah. Um, so, anybody listening,
check out down below. You'll see the
description. You could check out some
more of Sigmar. Um, check out his
YouTube. You guys down below. You can
check out Love Tuner, of course.
Anything else that may not be down there
that you want to uh send people towards
Sigmar?
>> Um, yeah. Like, uh, check out my book.
It's called One Journey. It's uh
published by Wateride. I have a copy
here. This is how it looks like. It's
available on Amazon and it's a quick
read and it's covers everything that we
talked about when it comes to frequency
breast work and also like you know some
spiritual guidelines that might be
helpful for people.
>> Right. And then did you say you're
writing a second one right now?
>> Uh no. This is my only one.
>> Okay. That one's already out. Okay. So
it's already out. They can get it now.
Cool.
>> Yeah.
>> Uh all right, brother. Well uh I'm gonna
end this recording. Everybody listening,
have a great day. Stretch, drink some
water, and check out Love Tuner and more
of Sigmar's work. We'll see you next
time.
Knowledge is power.
Reality is
>> Junkyard Love Not guest.